

CONTACT

- +94753531093 +94716603043
- wijethungalpcp@gmail.com
- 219, Moragaha Kanda,Wilegoda RD, Kalutara-North
- http://linkedin.com/in/chathulawijethunga-749009245
- https://chathulawijethunga.github .io/Home/

EDUCATION

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017 TECHNICAL COLLEGE- KALUTARA

 National certificate in Engineering Draughtsmanship NVQ 4

Jan 2022 - Dec 2024 COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY- COLOMBO

 National Diploma in Construction Technology NVQ 5

Jan 2023- Dec 2023 ARCHITECH CAD ACADEMY

• Diploma in BIM with Revit Architecture

April 2024
PROJECT MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE

Predictive Course

SKILLS

- AutoCAD
- BIM with Revit
- Project Management
- SDS 2
- Sketchup
- Lumion
- Photoshop
- MS-Office
- Construction Documents
- Space Planning
- Rough Estimates

LANGUAGES

- Sinhala (Fluent)
- English (Fluent)

CHATHULA WIJETHUNGA

BIM MODELER / CAD DRAUGHTSMAN

PROFILE

I am a smart working, dedicated individual with a sound academic knowledge and good communication skills. Working in large scale projects as a draftsman since 2018 and experienced in Architectural, Structural, and MEP drawings. I am also a good team worker with leadership skills who wish to collaborate with internal & external groups along with practical basis experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creatz Constructions

JAN 2021 - PRESENT

- Draughtsman
 - Communicate with clients and find client's requirements.
 - Site visit and understand the site situation.
 - · Create proposals for client's requirements.
 - · Develop selected models as drawings.
 - Submit council drawings for approval.
 - · Create detailed drawings for construction works.
 - Architectural Drawings.
 - Structural Drawings.
 - Service Drawings.

H&R Steel Detailing

Feb 2018 - Dec 2020

Structural Steel Detailer

- Analyzing building specifications, cords and regulations.
 - AICS steel construction manual.
 - OSHA standards.
 - Building Cords.
- Follow the contract documents and understand the scope.
- Coordinate with Architecture, Structural, MEP and Site staff.
- · Creating Erection Drawing, Member Details and Sub Material Drawing.
- Using SDS2, AutoCAD to create drawings and extract other documents.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

G.C.E Advanced Level Examination

2011

Tissa national college, Kalutara Done in mathematics stream

G.C.E Ordinary Level Examination

2008

Tissa national college, Kalutara

REFERENCE

Rev.Panapitiye Premarathana Thero (M.D.C.H Srilanka), J.P. (All Island)

Incumbent Thero,

Pavuranika Kande Vivekarama Maha Viharaya, Kaluthara-North. +94 34 222 8983

H. Ravindu sathsara Perera

Project Manager - Aesthetics & Co

+94 77 711 3267